<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<game>
  <title>Meridian: Frontier</title>
  <release-date>TBA</release-date>
  <website>https://store.steampowered.com/app/2541530/Meridian_Frontier/?utm_source=presskit&utm_campaign=announcement</website>

  <!-- Link to request press copy: -->
  <press-copy-request></press-copy-request>

  <platforms>
    <platform>
      <name>TBA</name>
      <link></link>
    </platform>
  </platforms>

  <prices>
    <price>
      <currency>TBA</currency>
      <value></value>
    </price>
  </prices>

  <description>
	  Meridian: Frontier is a story-driven 'lite-survival' base-building adventure game with a unique low-poly ¾ view style and deep, systemic gameplay. 
	  Explore a futuristic sci-fi underground world to mine and prospect for the valuable resources you need to build up your mining colony.
  </description>

  <!-- Choose between a single block: -->
  <history>
	  After leaving the AAA games industry, Alex's first project of his own always had to be a sci-fi survival game. 
	  Inspired both by classics like Lego Rock Raiders and modern survival gems like Subnautica, Meridian: Frontier is a love letter 
	  to story-driven singleplayer exploration, built around compelling physics-based gathering and base-building features.
  </history>

  <!-- Or multiple blocks: -->
  <!-- 
  <histories>
    <history>
      <header></header>
      <text></text>
    </history>
  </histories>
  -->

  <features>
    <feature>
		Stylised low-poly, high-fidelity graphics powered by Unreal Engine 5. 
	</feature> 
    <feature> 
		Mine and prospect for resources in a compelling, physics-based, futuristic sci-fi world.
	</feature>
    <feature>
		Build up a mining colony - construct buildings and facilities, acquire new plans and decorate with extensive cosmetic options.
	</feature>
    <feature>
		'Lite-survival' gameplay. No food or drink to manage, but the planet is a hostile environment and it won't be easy to make your fortune.
	</feature> 
	  <feature>
		Deep, story-driven exploration - follow in the boot-prints of a previous expedition and navigate a world of dystopian ultra-capitalism.
	</feature> 
    <feature>
		Riveting narrative and world-building driven by themes of corporate greed and the hope of a fresh start.
	</feature>
    <feature>
		Mine, collect, prospect, refine and craft a huge amount of resources, items and tools.
	</feature>
    <feature>
		Upgrade your tools and mining suit to unlock new abilities and improve your efficiency.
	</feature>
	  <feature>
		Fully voice-acted and featuring an original 'space-celtic' soundtrack.
	</feature>
  </features>
	
<trailers>
	<trailer>
		<name>Meridian: Frontier - Announce Trailer</name>

		<!-- Pick one: -->
		<youtube>
			UqILzqs27BA
		</youtube>

	</trailer>
	<trailer>
		<name>Meridian: Frontier - Gameplay Sizzle Reel</name>

		<!-- Pick one: -->
		<youtube>
			wKIN78cM6MQ
		</youtube>

	</trailer>
</trailers>

  <!-- You can set your widgets here (optional): -->
  <widgets>
    <steam>
		2541530
	</steam>
  </widgets>

  <credits>
    <credit>
      <person>Alex Kane</person>
      <role>Solo-Developer</role>
    </credit>
	  <credit>
      <person>Lisa Venturini</person>
      <role>2D Art</role>
    </credit>	    
	  <credit>
      <person>Kenned Gadelha</person>
      <role>Concept Art</role>
    </credit> 
	  <credit>
      <person>Madison James Smith</person>
      <role>Composer</role>
    </credit>
	  <credit>
      <person>Daniel Bletherwick</person>
      <role>Audio Design</role>
    </credit>
  </credits>
 
</game>
